perfumeemporium.com 2016-12-07

# Perfume Emporium - Cheap Perfume, Cologne, Skincare, Makeup, Haircare, and Fragrances!

**Perfume Emporium** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Perfume Emporium. 

Last Revised: 03/18/2013

_ORDER FORMS_  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases and information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. **_We never sell or rent customer's personal or financial information to third parties without a customer's prior consent._**

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is also used to bill the user for products and services.

We may also share your information, including your name, address, email address, and any transactions you conduct on our site or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver you advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain other websites. 

_SURVEYS_  
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address). 

Contact information from the surveys is used to ship purchases and information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material to our customers, and to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. We never sell or rent customer's personal or financial information to third parties without customers prior consent. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

_SECURITY_  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. _**All Online transactions are protected by secure server software.**_

_CHOICE/OPT-OUT_  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing emails and mailings from us. 

You can send email to sales@perfumeemporium.com. Type **"REMOVE FROM LIST"** in subject heading. 

_COOKIES_  
We regularly use cookies. A "cookie" is a small file stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow us to recognize who you are, when you arrive at our site, by associating an anonymous identification number in the cookie. At no time is your personally identifiable information stored within one of our cookies.

Cookies allow us to understand how you clicked to our site and what pages you click on during your visit to our site. Understanding how you shop allows us to improve and personalize your shopping experience and speed your checkout process. We may use our own cookies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of advertising provided by Perfume Emporium, click here.

Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, we may not be able to provide you with as good of an experience as one that is specifically tailored to your needs by utilizing the cookie.

_ADVERTISERS_  
We contract with a third-party advertising partner to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partner, click here. Opting out will not in any way effect your use of our site. 

_CHILDREN_  
The site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide personal information through the site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without parental consent. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

_UPDATES_  
This Privacy statement is subject to change. Please review it periodically. If we make changes to the privacy statement, we will revise the "Last Revised" date at the top of this statement. Any changes to this statement will become effective when we post the revised statement on the site. Your use of the Site following these changes means that you accept the revised statement. 

_CONTACTING THE WEB SITE_  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: sales@perfumeemporium.com 

Product names, logos, brands, and other trademarks featured or referred to within the http://www.perfumeemporium.com website are the property of their respective trademark holders. These trademark holders are not affiliated with Perfume Emporium, or our website.
